jumbled_list=[

    {
        "question": '''ivettceed
        Meaning of the word : a person who investigates crimes and gathers information''',
        "answer": "detective",
    },


    {
        "question": '''uspssnee
        Meaning of the word : a state or feeling of excited or anxious uncertainty about what may happen''',
        "answer": "suspense",
    },

    {
        "question": '''luce
        Meaning of the word : a piece of evidence or information used in the detection of a crime''',
        "answer": "clue",
    },

    {
        "question": '''iliab
        Meaning of the word : a claim or piece of evidence that one was elsewhere when an act, especially a criminal one, is alleged to have taken place''',
        "answer": "alibi",
    },

    {
        "question": '''pcrctyi
        Meaning of the word : having a meaning that is mysterious or obscure''',
        "answer": "cryptic",
    },

    {
        "question": '''etasgvteiin
        Meaning of the word : carry out a systematic or formal inquiry to discover and examine the facts of (an incident, allegation, etc.) so as to establish the truth
''',
        "answer": "investigate",
    },

    {
        "question": '''eitgrrnotae
        Meaning of the word : ask questions of (someone) closely, aggressively, or formally''',
        "answer": "interrogate",
    },

    {
        "question": '''srfcoeni
        Meaning of the word : relating to or denoting the application of scientific methods and techniques to the investigation of crime''',
        "answer": "forensic",
    },

    {
        "question": '''oncfsire
        Meaning of the word : give (someone or oneself) a different appearance in order to conceal one's identity''',
        "answer": "disguise",
    },

    {
        "question": '''nsstiwe
        Meaning of the word : a person who sees an event, typically a crime or accident, take place''',
        "answer": "witness",
    },

    {
        "question": '''evnrsleacuil
        Meaning of the word : close observation, especially of a suspected spy or criminal''',
        "answer": "surveillance",
    },

    {
        "question": '''tmesitnyo
        Meaning of the word : a formal written or spoken statement, especially one given in a court of law''',
        "answer": "testimony",
    },

    {
        "question": '''aenxime
        Meaning of the word : inspect (someone or something) thoroughly in order to determine their nature or condition''',
        "answer": "examine",
    },

    {
        "question": '''nivedece
        Meaning of the word : something that furnishes proof''',
        "answer": "evidence",
    },

    {
        "question": '''scpstue
        Meaning of the word : have an idea or impression of the existence, presence, or truth of (something) without certain proof''',
        "answer": "suspect",
    },

    {
        "question": '''zzpelu
        Meaning of the word : a game, toy, or problem designed to test ingenuity or knowledge''',
        "answer": "puzzle",
    },

    {
        "question": '''omrans
        Meaning of the word : a sum of money demanded or paid for the release of a captive''',
        "answer": "ransom",
    },

    {
        "question": '''deyco
        Meaning of the word : lure or entice (a person or animal) away from their intended course, typically into a trap''',
        "answer": "decoy",
    },

    {
        "question": '''yrymste
        Meaning of the word : something that is difficult or impossible to understand or explain''',
        "answer": "mystery",
    },

    {
        "question": '''eyrofgr
        Meaning of the word : the action of forging a copy or imitation of a document, signature, banknote, or work of art''',
        "answer": "forgery",
    },

    {
        "question": '''remic
        Meaning of the word : the intentional commission of an act usually deemed socially harmful or dangerous and specifically defined, prohibited, and punishable under criminal law''',
        "answer": "crime",
    },

    {
        "question": '''dverruonec
        Meaning of the word : involving secret work within a community or organization, especially for the purposes of police investigation or espionage''',
        "answer": "undercover",
    },

    {
        "question": '''yps
        Meaning of the word : a person employed by a government or other organization to secretly obtain information on an enemy or competitor''',
        "answer": "spy",
    },

    {
        "question": '''oclacipmec
        Meaning of the word : a person who helps another commit a crime''',
        "answer": "accomplice",
    },

    {
        "question": '''riplutc
        Meaning of the word : a person who is responsible for a crime or other misdeed''',
        "answer": "culprit",
    },

    {
        "question": '''ylbteara
        Meaning of the word : the action of betraying one's country, a group, or a person; treachery''',
        "answer": "betrayal",
    },

    {
        "question": '''nolwbgu
        Meaning of the word : a tube through which a projectile (such as a dart) may be impelled by the force of the breath''',
        "answer": "blowgun",
    },

    {
        "question": '''tsoipl
        Meaning of the word : a small firearm designed to be held in one hand''',
        "answer": "pistol",
    },

    {
        "question": '''lerif
        Meaning of the word : a gun, especially one fired from shoulder level, having a long spirally grooved barrel intended to make a bullet spin and thereby have greater accuracy over a long distance''',
        "answer": "rifle",
    },

    {
        "question": '''ygurbral
        Meaning of the word : illegal entry of a building with intent to commit a crime, especially theft''',
        "answer": "burglary",
    },

    {
        "question": '''rrbyali
        Meaning of the word : a building or room containing collections of books, periodicals, and sometimes films and recorded music for use or borrowing by the public or the members of an institution''',
        "answer": "library",
    },

    {
        "question": '''fegtuivi
        Meaning of the word : a person who has escaped from captivity or is in hiding
''',
        "answer": "fugitive",
    },

    {
        "question": '''rsamraewon
        Meaning of the word : a type of malicious software (malware) that threatens to publish or blocks access to data or a computer system, usually by encrypting it, until the victim pays a ransom fee to the attacker''',
        "answer": "ransomware",
    },

    {
        "question": '''brbiery
        Meaning of the word : offering, giving, receiving, or soliciting of any item of value to influence the actions of an official, or other person, in charge of a public or legal duty and to incline him to act contrary to his duty and the known rules of honesty and integrity''',
        "answer": "bribery",
    },

    {
        "question": '''omabolrl
        Meaning of the word : a large room for formal dancing''',
        "answer": "ballroom",
    },

    {
        "question": '''rumedr
        Meaning of the word : the unlawful premeditated killing of one human being by another''',
        "answer": "murder",
    },

     {
        "question": '''icmitv
        Meaning of the word : a person harmed, injured, or killed as a result of a crime, accident, or other event or action''',
        "answer": "victim",
    },

     {
        "question": '''aopnwe
        Meaning of the word : a thing designed or used for inflicting bodily harm or physical damage''',
        "answer": "weapon",
    },

     {
        "question": '''ensce
        Meaning of the word : the place where an incident in real life or fiction occurs or occurred''',
        "answer": "scene",
    },

     {
        "question": '''venrioynt
        Meaning of the word : all the items, goods, merchandise, and materials held by a business for selling in the market to earn a profit''',
        "answer": "inventory",
    },

     {
        "question": '''torpetarrep
        Meaning of the word : a person who carries out a harmful, illegal, or immoral act
''',
        "answer": "perpetrator",
    },

     {
        "question": '''npoios
        Meaning of the word : a substance that is capable of causing the illness or death of a living organism when introduced or absorbed''',
        "answer": "poison",
    },

     {
        "question": '''enfipntrirg
        Meaning of the word : ''',
        "answer": "fingerprint",
    },

     {
        "question": '''neeergv
        Meaning of the word : an impression or mark made on a surface by a person's fingertip, able to be used for identifying individuals from the unique pattern of whorls and lines on the fingertips''',
        "answer": "revenge",
    },

     {
        "question": '''sreart
        Meaning of the word : take them away to ask them about a crime that they might have committed''',
        "answer": "arrest",
    },

     {
        "question": '''tialr
        Meaning of the word : a formal examination of evidence by a judge, typically before a jury, in order to decide guilt in a case of criminal or civil proceedings''',
        "answer": "trial",
    },

     {
        "question": '''ujegd
        Meaning of the word : a public officer appointed to decide cases in a law court''',
        "answer": "judge",
    },

     {
        "question": '''yltigu
        Meaning of the word : culpable of or responsible for a specified wrongdoing''',
        "answer": "guilty",
    },

     {
        "question": '''bnbtiags
        Meaning of the word : an act or instance of wounding or killing someone with a knife''',
        "answer": "stabbing",
    },

     {
        "question": '''eicomdhi
        Meaning of the word : the killing of one human being by another''',
        "answer": "homicide",
    },

     {
        "question": '''enusiqt
        Meaning of the word : a judicial inquiry to ascertain the facts relating to an incident''',
        "answer": "inquest",
    },

     {
        "question": '''ueiencotx
        Meaning of the word : the carrying out of a plan, order, or course of action''',
        "answer": "execution",
    },

     {
        "question": '''yctsudo
        Meaning of the word : the protective care or guardianship of someone or something''',
        "answer": "custody",
    },

     {
        "question": '''syaialsn
        Meaning of the word : detailed examination of the elements or structure of something''',
        "answer": "analysis",
    },

     {
        "question": '''cootrpol
        Meaning of the word : the official procedure or system of rules governing affairs of state or diplomatic occasions''',
        "answer": "protocol",
    },

     {
        "question": '''hekcts
        Meaning of the word : a rough or unfinished drawing or painting, often made to assist in making a more finished picture''',
        "answer": "sketch",
    },

     {
        "question": '''eracifepl
        Meaning of the word : a place for a domestic fire, especially a grate or hearth at the base of a chimney''',
        "answer": "fireplace",
    },


    {
        "question": '''kenfi
        Meaning of the word : an instrument composed of a blade fixed into a handle, used for cutting or as a weapon''',
        "answer": "knife",
    },
]